<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="inveta_snippet.about_us" model="website.page">
            <field name="name">About</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="url">/about</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="key">inveta_snippet.about_us</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="About" t-name="inveta_snippet.about_us">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div class="oe_structure"/>
                        <section class="s_cover parallax bg-black-50 pt96 pb96" data-scroll-background-ratio="1">
                            <span class="s_parallax_bg oe_img_bg"
                                  style="background-image: url('/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/bannnn-01.jpg');"/>
                            <div class="container s_allow_columns">
                                <h1 style="text-align: center;">
                                    <font style="font-size: 62px; font-weight: bold;">INVETA GROUP</font>
                                </h1>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                        <section class="py-12 md:py-24 lg:py-32">
                            <div class="container grid items-center gap-4 px-4 md:px-6">
                                <div class="space-y-3">
                                    <h2 class="text-3xl font-bold tracking-tighter md:text-4xl" style="color: #d85426;">
                                        We are a renowned economic development firm in Africa
                                    </h2>
                                    <p class="max-w-[600px] text-gray-500 md:text-xl/relaxed lg:text-base/relaxed xl:text-xl/relaxed dark:text-gray-400">
                                        Specializing in investment promotion, Project Finance and Inter- intra Africa
                                        trade facilitation.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="rounded-lg border bg-card text-card-foreground shadow-sm"
                                     t-attf-data-v0-t="card">
                                    <div class="p-6">
                                        <p class="text-gray-500 mt-2">
                                            We are a leading catalyst for economic development committed to providing
                                            best-in-class services that
                                            drive economic growth, enhance market access and finance whilst promoting
                                            sustainable developments in
                                            Africa. We create value by offering comprehensive solutions, leveraging our
                                            expertise, and fostering
                                            meaningful partnerships.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                            </div>
                        </section>
                        <section class="team-body">
                            <div class="team-section">
                                <h1 class="team-heading">Our Team</h1>
                                <p class="team-description">
                                    INVETA Group boasts a highly skilled and experienced team that guides the company's
                                    strategic direction and ensures the successful execution of projects and
                                    initiatives. Our leaders bring diverse backgrounds and expertise, enabling us to
                                    deliver comprehensive solutions to our clients. With a deep understanding of the
                                    African landscape and a commitment to excellence, our team fosters a culture of
                                    innovation, collaboration, and client-centricity.
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                        <section class="team-section py-5">
                            <div class="container mt-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <!-- Profile Card 1 -->
                                    <div class="col-md-6">
                                        <div class="profile-card text-center">
                                            <img alt=" "
                                                 class="rounded-circle"
                                                 src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/uju_paulsy_inveta.jpg"/>
                                            <h2>UJU PAULCY</h2>
                                            <h3>CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER</h3>
                                            <p>Uju Paulcy is a business executive deeply committed to promoting economic
                                                development in Africa. She is the founder of the INVETA Group and also
                                                serves as the host and executive producer of Invest and Trade Africa.
                                                With over 10 years of experience in the industry, Uju is widely
                                                recognized as an expert communicator in international trade, finance,
                                                investment, energy and the oil and gas industry. She has offered
                                                insights through Invest and Trade Africa and other notable platforms to
                                                governments, businesses, and organizations on a wide range of issues,
                                                including trade policy, investment promotion, and economic development
                                                strategies.

                                                Through her work as an advocate for Africa’s economic potential, she is
                                                helping to build a brighter future for Africa and the world at large.
                                            </p>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <!-- Profile Card 2 -->
                                    <div class="col-md-6">
                                        <div class="profile-card text-center">
                                            <img alt=" "
                                                 class="rounded-circle"
                                                 src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/ugo.jpg"/>
                                            <h2>UGO NWOFOR</h2>
                                            <h3>LEGAL ADVISORY</h3>
                                            <p>Ugo Nwofor is a legal practitioner, Notary Public and Strategy
                                                Consultant. With more than 21 years of active and sound legal practice,
                                                Ugo's experience is creditably pronounced. He is one of the founding
                                                partners of Wealthy Partners, a firm of astute and profound legal
                                                Practitioners and is currently the Managing Partner of the Firm.

                                                As a seasoned professional, Ugo has provided strategic counsel and
                                                guidance to numerous organizations across various industries. His
                                                ability to identify opportunities, mitigate risks, and devise effective
                                                strategies has been instrumental in driving organizational growth and
                                                success. As a valued member of our Board, he brings invaluable insights,
                                                and a commitment to excellence that enhances and strengthens our
                                                corporate governance
                                            </p>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>


                            </div>
                            <div class="container mt-5">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <!-- Profile Card 1 -->
                                    <div class="col-md-6">
                                        <div class="profile-card text-center">
                                            <img alt=" "
                                                 class="rounded-circle"
                                                 src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/joannah.jpg"/>
                                            <h2>JOANNAH TITUS</h2>
                                            <h3>INVESTMENT PROMOTION and FACILITATION OFFICER</h3>
                                            <p>Joannah Titus is a highly skilled lawyer specializing in business
                                                development and facilitation at INVETA Group. In her role as the
                                                Business Development and Facilitation Officer at INVETA Group, Joannah
                                                brings together her legal expertise and business acumen to drive
                                                successful investment promotion and facilitation outcomes for the
                                                company and its various partners.

                                                She has extensive experience in inter and intra African trade, oil and
                                                gas industry and the energy sector. As a seasoned lawyer, her legal
                                                expertise includes but is not limited to; Dispute Resolution,
                                                International Trade and Corporate/Commercial law with specifics in
                                                contract drafting and negotiation, regulatory compliance in the oil and
                                                gas industry, due diligence on investment projects and assessing legal
                                                risks.
                                            </p>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <!-- Profile Card 2 -->
                                    <div class="col-md-6">
                                        <div class="profile-card md:height-500 lg:height-500 xl:height-500 text-center">
                                            <img alt=" "
                                                 class="rounded-circle"
                                                 src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/ifeyinwa.jpg"/>
                                            <h2>IFEYINWA NKAMNEBE</h2>
                                            <h3>PROGRAM EXECUTIVE</h3>
                                            <p>Ifeyinwa is the Program Executive at INVETA Group. She is a business
                                                administrative manager with years of experience in different sector of
                                                the economy; oil and gas industry, insurance and the banking sector. She
                                                is effective in initiating and implementing healthy ideas that ensure
                                                seamless business operations and client satisfaction.

                                                She has had experience in leading and managing programs focused on
                                                promoting investment, economic growth and sustainable development in
                                                Africa. In her career, she has executed a myriad of multifaceted
                                                programs that has attracted international investors to the African
                                                economy.
                                            </p>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>


                            </div>


                        </section>
                        <section>
                            <div class="team-section mt-5">
                                <div class="row text-center" style="color: #d85426;">
                                    <h2>Finance Partners</h2>
                                    <p>

                                    </p>
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <!-- Team Member 1 -->
                                        <div class="col-md-4 items-center">
                                            <div class="card-fin">
                                                <img alt="Placeholder image of Flora Nyra" class="card-img-top"
                                                     height="300"
                                                     src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/ahmed.jpg" width="300"/>
                                                <h5 class="card-title-fin">DR. AHMED ELGAWISH</h5>
                                                <p>
                                                    Managing Director
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <!-- Team Member 2 -->
                                        <div class="col-md-4">
                                            <div class="card-fin">
                                                <img alt="Placeholder image of Evander Mac" class="card-img-top"
                                                     height="300" src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/nevine.jpg"
                                                     width="300"/>
                                                <h5 class="card-title-fin">DR. NEVINE NAKHLA</h5>
                                                <p>
                                                    Public Affairs Director
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <!-- Team Member 3 -->
                                        <div class="col-md-4">
                                            <div class="card-fin">
                                                <img alt="Placeholder image of Taytum Elia" class="card-img-top"
                                                     height="300" src="/inveta_snippet/static/src/img/wael.jpg"
                                                     width="300"/>
                                                <h5 class="card-title-fin">DR. WAEL SWELAM</h5>
                                                <p>
                                                    VIP Technical
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                        <!--                        <section class="bg-light py-3 py-md-5 py-xl-8">-->


                        <div class="oe_structure"/>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>